Hazmin Jin



Contact

City:

Kuala Lumpur

Country:

Malaysia

Email:

kingdev10260522@gmail.com

Skype:

live:.cid.46511127d610143a

Github:

https://github.com/KingDev1026/

Languages

English

Summary

Experienced blockchain and full stack developer, 3 years of blockchain experience, 6 years of full stack experience.

Working with Fungible & Non-Fungible tokens on Several Networks (Ethereum, Solana, Binance Smart Chain, Polygon, ...)

Building smart contracts by solidity, rust and building Websites using web3.js.

Have rich experiences in developing Defi, Dapp- Stable coin Launch, Mint&Burn, Staking, Bridge,Swapping, Market Platforms.

Working as Frontend&Backend developer, built websites for Ecommerce, education etc.

EXPERIENCE

Web3 Developer

(https://skybridger.io/ & https://rewards.skybridger.io/)

Skybridger is bridging between casper and binance token.

- Build skybridger website and build bridge smart contracts.
- Build website for metamask admin sigin every month so they sign to receive bridge fees.

01/2022-current

Senior Blockchain&Full Stack Engineer

(https://www.tacocat.co/)

Wtacocat is a company stands for bringing cropto to the Mainstream with the aim to make crypto more accessible and easier to understand. They are building crypto game platforms called WildcardGame.

- Launch Tokens called WCT which will be the main token of game and built website for presale.
- Lanuch NFT tokens called WildCardOrb which will be the character token of the game and built website for minting.
- Launch Deck tokens which will be used as a membership on the game and built website for buy the token.

06/2021-12/2021

Senior Blockchain Engineer.

(https://fatcatmafia.io/)

Fat Cat Mafia is a collection of 2222 slightly overweight unique kitten, that run the most notorious crime structure on the Solana Blockchain.

- Lanuch NFT tokens called FatCatMafia which will be the character token of the maket place and built website for minting.

02/2020-05/2021

Skills

Blockchain

Solidity Rust Hardhat Truffle Remix NFT Web3.js IPFS Token(ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155, BEP20) uniswap pancakeswap Dapp

Web/ Desktop

HTML5 CSS3 Tailwind CSS PHP Laravel Symfony JavaScript/ ES6&ES8 Angular JS React.js Redux Vue.js Next.js Nuxt.js Ember.js Backbone.js D3.js TypeScript Node.js Express.js Java Python Django Golang C++ C# .NET ASP.NET SQL GraphQL

Mobile

iOS Android Java Swift RxSwift RxCocoa Objective-C React Native Flutter Kotlin Ionic/ Cordova Xamarin

DB/ Tools/ Methodologies

MySQL PostgreSQL MongoDB RESTful API Docker Azure AWS/ EC2/ S3 ElasticSearch Microservices OOP/ MVC/ MVVM Scrum/ Agile CI/ CD DevOps Github GitLab Bitbucket Jira Trello Jenkins

Senior Solidity & Web3.js Developer.

(https://savagesharks.io/)

Savage Sharks are a collection of 5,555 randomly generated Savage Sharks NFTs on the Solana Network. The 5,555 Savage Sharks create our community known as The shiver. Our Savage Sharks are mean, tough, ripped, beasts of the ocean. Savage Sharks are known for eating all the oceans creatures and creating a deadly sea!

- Lanuch NFT tokens called Savage sharks that will be a character token for the blockchain community and shark game and will build a website for issuance.
- Make a smart contract so that users of the Savage Sharks NFTs can create other NFT.
- -Create contracts for NFT bridging and staking.

10/2019-04/2021

Web Frontend Developer

(https://nrg-soft.com/)

Created reusable D3.js charts using Raphael.js to draw SVG on browsers. Handled responsive design layouts for views.

Implemented reusable components for UX using jQuery.

Worked with a React/Redux environment on a major enterprise product already in production.

Helped integrate charts libraries based on D3 and React. TECHNOLOGIES: GraphQL, JavaScript, HTML5, Web Development, MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, Redux, React, Babel, D3.js.

03/2019-08/2019

Junior Web Developer

(https://setronica.com/)

Did advanced JavaScript functional programming.

Designed a MongoDB database.

Created single-page apps with Backbone.js and Ember.js.

Developed software using RESTful APIs with Node.js and Express.js.

Handled JavaScript UX framework prototyping.

Added a Hot module replacement plugin to Webpack.

 ${\sf TECHNOLOGIESO\ HTML5,\ CSS,\ JavaScript,\ BootStrap,\ Backbone.js,}$

Ember.js, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB, RESTful APIs.

06/2018-07/2019

Senior Blockchain Engineer.

successfully reached the phase-1 of the Project.

(https://www.monstersclan.com/)

Performed initial client assessment and analysis to begin research process. Supported Chief Operating Officer with daily operational functions. defined the structure of the Blockchain Development for the Product team and defined the Access controls and security and environment for the Almaty. Designed and developed the smart contracts using the Solidity and implemented test scripts on the smart contracts using the truffle framework. optimized the smart contract code and increased the efficiency by 15%, using the Library functionalities of the solidity.

05/2017-05/2018

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

International University of Malaya (2013-2017)

 Relevant Coursework: Programming Methodology, Discrete Structures, Data Structures and Algorithms, Computer Orgamisation, Software Engineering, Introduction to Computer Networks, Introduction to Operating Systems, Introducton to Information security